Joseph Keppler Jr. Iroquois papers,1882-1944.
Keppler Jr, Joseph, Iroquois papers,1882-1944.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph Keppler Jr. Iroquois papers, 1882-1944.
9184
Udo J., Keppler 1872-1956.
3 cubic ft.; 3 boxes.
Correspondence, Newspapers, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Primarily letters to Keppler, including a record of events and people at the Tonawanda and Cattaraugus reservations, among others, over the first part of the twentieth century. Well known correspondents include noted Seneca scholar, Arthur C. Parker; artist, Jesse Cornplanter; and Mohawk poet, E. Pauline Johnson. Other parts of the collection include newspapers clippings on Iroquois subjects, government documents, Seneca vocabulary collected by Keppler, and other miscellaneous documents related to the Iroquois and the Six Nations. Newspaper clippings, obituaries, pamphlets, photographs, and notes are included with the correspondence. Collection contains indexes of correspondents chronologically as well as a card file of correspondents listed alphabetically. Other information includes correspondence about the collection itself, biographic information about the correspondents, clippings and documents regarding New York State land claims by the Caughnawagas and Saint Regis Indians, The New York State Museum, genealogic information, obituaries, clippings about the Wanamaker National Indian Memorial, photographs of a silver cross pendent, and correspondence regarding Iroquois masks.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Udo Keppler was a political cartoonist for Puck Magazine, and an avid collector of Indian artifacts as well as being an Indian activist. He changed his name to Joseph Keppler, Jr. in honor of his father. He was elected honorary chief of Seneca and given the name Gyantwaka. He actively promoted Iroquois lacrosse teams, and his connections with the railroad enabled him to procure discount railroad passes for New York Indians, especially those travelling to Canada on Confederacy business. On the national scene, Keppler worked with others to defeat or substantially modify proposed legislation allot the New York State reservations.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Primarily letters to Keppler, including a record of events and people at the Tonawanda and Cattaraugus reservations, among others, over the first part of the twentieth century. Well known correspondents include noted Seneca scholar, Arthur C. Parker; artist, Jesse Cornplanter; and Mohawk poet, E. Pauline Johnson. Other parts of the collection include newspapers clippings on Iroquois subjects, government documents, Seneca vocabulary collected by Keppler, and other miscellaneous documents related to the Iroquois and the Six Nations. Newspaper clippings, obituaries, pamphlets, photographs, and notes are included with the correspondence. Collection contains indexes of correspondents chronologically as well as a card file of correspondents listed alphabetically. Other information includes correspondence about the collection itself, biographic information about the correspondents, clippings and documents regarding New York State land claims by the Caughnawagas and Saint Regis Indians, The New York State Museum, genealogic information, obituaries, clippings about the Wanamaker National Indian Memorial, photographs of a silver cross pendent, and correspondence regarding Iroquois masks.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Keppler, Udo J.,1872-1956.; Bates, Erl Augustus Caesar, 1889-1973; Burnett, Edwin Kenneth.; Converse, Harriet Maxwell, 1836-1903.; Cornplanter, Jesse J.; Doxon, Charles.; Hartman, Cary W.; Heye, George G.(George Gustav), 1874-1957; Hiawatha, 15th cent.; Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948.; Johnson, E. Pauline, 1861-1913.; Keppler, Joseph Ferdinand, 1838-1894.; Lummis, Charles Fletcher, 1859-1928.; Parker, Arthur Caswell, 1881-1955; Parker, Ely Samuel, 1828-1895.; Pierce, Ulysses G. B.(Ulysses Grant Baker), 1865-1943.; Seitz, Don Carlos, 1862-1935.; Sundown, Arnold.; Taft, Grace Ellis.; Wanamaker, Rodman, 1863-1928.; Huntington Free Library.; New York State Museum.; Six Nations.; West Shore Railroad Company.
Subjects:
Indians of North America.; Indians of North America--Claims.; Indians of North America; Indians of North America--Dwellings.; Indians of North America--Government relations.; Indians of North America--Kansas.; Indians of North America--New York (State).; Indians of North America--Sports.; Indian masks--North America.; Iroquois Indians.; Iroquois language.; Mohawk Indians.; Mohawk language.; Seneca Indians.; Seneca language.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
The Joseph Keppler papers reflect the long association Keppler had with the Iroquois peoples, principally the Seneca, of New York State. The earliest papers in the Library date from 1882; they continue through 1944, when Keppler remarried and left New York, giving his papers to the Library of the Museum of the American Indian, Heye Foundation. The collection is calendared chronologically; the papers are arranged by correspondent. Keppler carried on active correspondence with several individuals over a significant period of time. As the collection is primarily their letters to Keppler, this correspondence is a record of events and people at the Tonawanda and Cattaraugus reservations, among others, over the first part of the twentieth century. Well-known correspondents include noted Seneca scholar, Arthur C. Parker; artist, Jesse Cornplanter; and Mohawk poet, E. Pauline Johnson. Other parts of the collection include newspapers clippings on Iroquois subjects, government documents, Seneca vocabulary collected by Keppler, and other miscellaneous documents related to the Iroquois.
Keppler, a political cartoonist for Puck Magazine, was an avid collector of Indian artifacts. This interest led him to an association with George Heye, director of the Museum of the American Indian. Keppler often acted as an intermediary between other collectors and Native artisans, facilitating the expansion of the Iroquois collection of the Museum of the American Indian and others. He played an active role in the lives of many Seneca (and some Onondaga) individuals. At the death of Harriet Converse in 1903, he was chosen by the Seneca as her successor. Both he and those who wrote to him used his Seneca name regularly. Many envelopes in the Keppler papers are simply addressed "Gyantwaka, Puck Building, N.Y.C." His concern for his Seneca friends was manifested on both personal and political levels. Letters to him are full of thanks for monetary gifts and donations of clothing, and bring him up to date with family news as well. He actively promoted Iroquois lacrosse teams, and his connections with the railroad enabled him to procure discount railroad passes for New York Indians, especially those travelling to Canada on Confederacy business. On the national scene, Keppler worked with others to defeat or substantially modify proposed legislation allot the New York State reservations. His papers indicate he was most involved with Seneca issues and people in the first two decades of the twentieth century. He continued his interest in Iroquois people into the 1940s, more or less concluding the period reflected in these papers with the publication in 1941 of Comments on Certain Iroquois Masks by the Museum of the American Indian, Heye Foundation.
Iroquoian scholars have often used the Keppler papers in doing research on prominent individuals, such as Arthur C. Parker. They will find the correspondence to Keppler also provides a rich picture of life on the Seneca reservations in the early twentieth century.
Objects associated with this collection are at the National Museum of the American Indian.
RELATED MATERIALS
Microfilm available.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Printed Guides
Box 1
Series II. Correspondence
Boxes 1-2
Series III. Other Material
Box 3
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Printed Guides
  Some of these guides offer content details and item level descriptions of the correspondence. The chronological listing is available as an online searchable PDF.
  - Table of Contents (Box 1)
  - Old catalog (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals A-C (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals D-I (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals J (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals K-M (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals N-R (Box 1)
  - Alphabetical listing of individuals S-Z (Box 1)
  - Chronological listing 1882-1903 (Box 1, Folder A)
    Link to a copy of this listing. (4 MB Searchable PDF)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 1
  - Chronological listing 1904-1908 (Box 1, Folder B)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 56
  - Chronological listing 1909-1918 (Box 1, Folder C)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 107
  - Chronological listing 1919-1933 (Box 1, Folder D)
    Link to a copy of this listing. (5 MB Searchable PDF)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 163
  - Chronological listing 1934-1944 (Box 1, Folder E)
    Link to a copy of this listing. (6 MB Searchable PDF)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 228
  - Catalog of individuals and number of items for each (Box 1, Folder F)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 308
  - Extra Calendars 1882-1907 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Extra Calendars 1908-1927 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Extra Calendars 1928-1937 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Extra Calendars 1938-1944 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Extra Calendars 1889-1907 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Extra Calendars 1908-1927 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Extra Calendars 1928-1937 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Extra Calendars 1938-1944 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Alphabetical index of correspondents on cards (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Abrams, Chauncey H., 1900-1905 (Box 1, Folder A2)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 316
  - Abrams, Frank, 1908 (Box 1, Folder A2.1)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 361
  - Bishop, Thomas G., 1921 (Box 1, Folder B4)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 365
  - Black, Barber, 1905-1906 (Box 1, Folder B6)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 369
  - Bowen, Charley, 1917 (Box 1, Folder B7)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 373
  - Bowen, Nancy, 1934 (Box 1, Folder B7.1)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 377
  - Converse, Harriet Maxwell-Letters (Box 1, Folder C6)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 396
  - Converse, Harriet Maxwell-Clippings relating to death and funeral (Box 1, Folder C6.A)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 484
  - Converse, Harriet Maxwell-Miscellaneous clippings (Box 1, Folder C6.B)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 550
  - Converse, Harriet Maxwell-Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder C6.M)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 629
  - Cook, Farnham, 1911-1929 (Box 1, Folder C7)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 640
  - Cooper, Moses, 1904 (Box 1, Folder C7.3)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 700
  - Chief Corenthe, 1904 (Box 1, Folder C8)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 705
  - Cornplanter, Edward (Box 1, Folder C8.3)
    Also available on Reel 1, Frame 713
  - Cornplanter, Jesse (Box 1, Folder C8.4)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 1
  - Cornplanter, Nancy (Box 1, Folder C8.5)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 202
  - Cornplanter, Nancy, 1906-1941 (Box 1, Folder C9)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 206
  - Crow, Julia, 1901-1903 (Box 1, Folder C9.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 219
  - Crow, William & Mrs., 1904 (Box 1, Folder C9.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 229
  - Davies or Davis, Mary, 1906 (Box 1, Folder D2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 233
  - Deerfoot matters (Box 1, Folder D3)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 239
  - Deerfoot matters (Box 1, Folder D3.M)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 279
  - Dibo, Frank, 1906-1908 (Box 1, Folder D5)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 287
  - Dibo, Mitchell, 1909 (Box 1, Folder D5.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 299
  - Doxon, Charles, 1905-1909 (Box 1, Folder D7)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 304
  - Doxtader, Orlando, 1900-1903 (Box 1, Folder D7.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 324
  - Doyle, Lewis J., 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder D8)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 331
  - Elm, A.A., 1905 (Box 1, Folder E7)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 344
  - Farmer, Mrs. Orris, 1905 (Box 1, Folder F2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 347
  - Fatty, Thomas, 1908 (Box 1, Folder F2.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 355
  - George, Simon, 1909-1911 (Box 1, Folder G3)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 358
  - Green, Louise (Box 1, Folder G8)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 365
  - Ground, Harrison, 1941 (Box 1, Folder G8.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 369
  - Halftown, James H., 1899 (Box 1, Folder H2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 374
  - Hartman, Cary W. matter [Includes correspondence from Arthur C. Parker, P2] (Box 1, Folder H2.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 379
  - Hartman, Cary W. matter [Includes correspondence from Arthur C. Parker] (Box 1, Folder H2.2.M)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 467
  - Hartman, Cary W. matter [Includes correspondence from Arthur C. Parker], 1911 (Box 1, Folder H3)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 483
  - Hemlock, Sackett, 1907-1913 (Box 1, Folder H3.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 487
  - Heye, George, 1944 (Box 2, Folder K3.J)
    Also available on Reel 3, apx. Frame 664
  - Hill, C.D., 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder H4)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 512
  - Hill, David R., 1904-1927 (Box 1, Folder H4.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 526
  - Hill, Elijah, 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder H4.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 541
  - Isaac, Harry, 1907-1923 (Box 1, Folder I8)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 561
  - Isaac, Reuben, 1940 (Box 1, Folder I8.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 569
  - Jacobs, George, 1909 (Box 1, Folder J1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 572
  - Jacobs, Jasper, 1909 (Box 1, Folder J1.1)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 575
  - Jacobs, Joseph, 1904 (Box 1, Folder J1.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 578
  - Jacobs, Sally, 1904 (Box 1, Folder J1.4)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 584
  - Jimerson, Howard, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder J3.2)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 595
  - Jimerson, Jacob M., 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder J3.3)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 611
  - Jimerson, Mrs. Walter, 1933-1936 (Box 1, Folder J3.5)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 643
  - John, Andrew, 1900-1905 (Box 1, Folder J5)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 651
  - John, Perry L, 1908 (Box 1, Folder J5.3)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 661
  - Johnson, Charles (Box 1, Folder J6)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 666
  - Johnson, Freeman (Box 1, Folder J6.4)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame 674
  - Johnson, Lyman (Box 1, Folder J6.6 #1-85)
    Also available on Reel 2, Frame
  - Johnson, Lyman (Box 1, Folder J6.6 #86-172)
  - Johnson, Lyman (Box 1, Folder J6.6 #173-252)
  - Johnson, Morses, 1904 (Box 2, Folder J7)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 1
  - Jones, Adam, 1901-1913 (Box 2, Folder J8)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 4
  - Jones, Gerry, 1908 (Box 2, Folder J8.2)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 29
  - Jones, Hiram, 1905 (Box 2, Folder J8.3)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 33
  - Jones, Jennie, 1931-1942 (Box 2, Folder J8.4)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 37
  - Jones, Orrin, 1901 (Box 2, Folder J8.6)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 53
  - Jones, R. Deforest, 1902 (Box 2, Folder J8.8)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 57
  - Jones, Sophia, 1935 (Box 2, Folder J8.9)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 62
  - Jones, Thomas E. (Box 2, Folder J8.9.2)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 66
  - Jordan, Margarette, 1911-1914 (Box 2, Folder J9)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 90
  - Kennedy, Charles, 1907-1912 (Box 2, Folder K2)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 128
  - Kennedy, Frank A. & Mrs., 1904 (Box 2, Folder K2.2)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 133
  - Kennedy, LeRoy W., 1908 (Box 2, Folder K2.5)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 141
  - Kennedy, Thomas H., 1901-1907 (Box 2, Folder K2.8)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 146
  - Keppler, Joseph-Correspondence (Box 2, Folder K3.A)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 161
  - Keppler, Joseph-Personal (Box 2, Folder K3.B)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 175
  - Keppler, Joseph-Speeches and Greetings (Box 2, Folder K3.C)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 209
  - Keppler, Joseph-Seneca Silver Star (Box 2, Folder K3.D)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 277
  - Keppler, Joseph-Ethnological notes and excerpts from source material (Box 2, Folder K3.E)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 330
  - Keppler, Joseph-Anecdotes, personal experiences (Box 2, Folder K3.F)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 506
  - Keppler, Joseph-Folklore (Box 2, Folder K3.G)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 521
  - Keppler, Joseph-Ceremonies (Box 2, Folder K3.H)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 585
  - Keppler, Joseph-Handsome Lake (Box 2, Folder K3.I)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 623
  - Keppler, Joseph-Newtown Long House Wampum (Box 2, Folder K3.J)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 664
  - Keppler, Joseph-Powers of attorney, etc. (Box 2, Folder K3.K)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 680
  - Keppler, Joseph-Little Water Society meeting notices (Box 2, Folder K3.L)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 688
  - Keppler, Joseph-Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder K3.M)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 724
  - King, Dinah Sundown (Box 2, Folder K4)
    Also available on Reel 3, Frame 841
  - Kittle, Delos (Box 2, Folder K5)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 1
  - Kittle, Jane, 1899 (Box 2, Folder K5.2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 182
  - Kittle, Louisa (Box 2, Folder K5.4)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 185
  - Kunz, George K., 1911 (Box 2, Folder K7)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 192
  - LaFrance, Noah, 1904 (Box 2, Folder L2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 200
  - Lay, Chester C., 1903-1904 (Box 2, Folder L3)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 204
  - Lay, Kelly, 1901-1904 (Box 2, Folder L3.2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 210
  - Lay, Moses, 1902 (Box 2, Folder L3.3)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 224
  - Lay, Skidmore, 1908 (Box 2, Folder L3.4)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 233
  - Lay, Mrs. Young, 1909 (Box 2, Folder L3.6)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 237
  - Logan, Alfred, 1904-1933 (Box 2, Folder L6)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 242
  - Logan, Frank, 1905-1910 (Box 2, Folder L6.2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 256
  - Longfeather, James, 1903-1904 (Box 2, Folder L7)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 268
  - Lummis, Charles F., 1911 (Box 2, Folder L8)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 284
  - Lyons, Anna C., 1935 (Box 2, Folder L9)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 288
  - Lyons, Jesse, 1912 (Box 2, Folder L9.3)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 293
  - Martin, Richmond, 1932-1942 (Box 2, Folder M2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 296
  - Meyer, Fred R., 1913 (Box 2, Folder M3)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 334
  - Miller, Thomas A., 1928 (Box 2, Folder M4)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 338
  - Moore, F.E., 1909 (Box 2, Folder M6)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 348
  - New York State Museum, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder N2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 352
  - Ninham, Fred & Mrs. (Box 2, Folder N4)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 360
  - Parker, Arthur. See also H2.2 (Box 2, Folder P2)
    Also available on Reel 4, Frame 658
  - Parker, Ely S. (Box 2, Folder P2.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 1
  - Patterson, A. E., 1904 (Box 2, Folder P2.5)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 25
  - Patterson, N. C., 1910 (Box 2, Folder P2.7)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 32
  - Phillips, Eliza, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder P5)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 44
  - Phillips, James, 1905 (Box 2, Folder P5.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 67
  - Pierce, George, 1901-1906 (Box 2, Folder P6.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 73
  - Pierce, Lucy G., 1902 (Box 2, Folder P6.4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 84
  - Pierce, Ulysses G., 1905 (Box 2, Folder P6.8)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 89
  - Red Eagle, Dan [LaFrance], 1905-1912 (Box 2, Folder R2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 93
  - Regis, Joseph, 1906 (Box 2, Folder R2.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 110
  - Rockwell, W. Honyoust, 1908 (Box 2, Folder R6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 114
  - Sandy, William (Box 2, Folder S2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 118
  - Saylor, Louis, 1903-? (Box 2, Folder S2.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 124
  - Schanandoah, Chapman (Box 2, Folder S3)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 135
  - Scanandoah, Enoch (Box 2, Folder S3.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 303
  - Schneider or Snyder, Leonard Everette. (Box 2, Folder S3.4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 332
  - Seitz, Don C, 1915 (Box 2, Folder S3.7)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 361
  - Shongo, Moses, 1900 (Box 2, Folder S4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 364
  - Skye, Fannie D., 1930 (Box 2, Folder S4.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 373
  - Skye, Solon, 1905-1906 (Box 2, Folder S4.5)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 379
  - Smith, Eva, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder S6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 387
  - Smith, Peter, 1904 (Box 2, Folder S6.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 416
  - Snyder, John L., 1908 (Box 2, Folder S6.6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 420
  - Solomon, Louis, 1914 (Box 2, Folder S7.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 423
  - Solomon, Michael, 1913 (Box 2, Folder S7.3)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 427
  - Stacey, Moses, 1909 (Box 2, Folder S8)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 432
  - Sundown, Arnold, 1936 (Box 2, Folder S8.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 438
  - Sundown, Charlotte, 1906-1910 (Box 2, Folder S8.3)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 442
  - Sundown, Jesse, 1933 (Box 2, Folder S8.5)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 448
  - Sundown, John, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder S8.6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 456
  - Taft, J. R., 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder T1)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 465
  - Tahamont, E., 1905 (Box 2, Folder T2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 476
  - Tallchief, William, 1904 (Box 2, Folder T2.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 479
  - Terrance, Peter D., 1904 (Box 2, Folder T3)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 482
  - Thomas, Baptist and Mrs., 1900-1917 (Box 2, Folder T4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 486
  - Thomas, Edward, 1905 (Box 2, Folder T4.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 506
  - Thomas, Electa, 1917 (Box 2, Folder T4.4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 509
  - Thompson, Salena, 1929 (Box 2, Folder T6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 514
  - Thompson, Samuel, 1912-1916 (Box 2, Folder T6.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 518
  - VanEvery, George and Mrs., 1908-1917 (Box 2, Folder V2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 530
  - Wanamaker Memorial (Box 2, Folder W1)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 568
  - Warrior, David (Box 2, Folder W2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 591
  - West Shore Railroad (Box 2, Folder W3)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 599
  - White, Alice (Box 2, Folder W4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 615
  - White, Clayton W. (Box 2, Folder W4.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 767
  - White, Grace D. (Box 2, Folder W4.4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 771
  - White Eagle, Joseph, 1905-1906 (Box 2, Folder W5)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 778
  - Williams, L.S., 1904 (Box 2, Folder W6.2)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 787
  - Williams, Spencer, 1906 (Box 2, Folder W6.4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 790
  - Wilson, George (Box 2, Folder W6.6)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 793
  - Wilson, Leroy, 1906 (Box 2, Folder W6.8)